disneyclips.com 2011-05-04

# Disneyclips.com - Privacy Policy

|  | 

| | 

---|---  

| 

| 

_**Privacy Policy**_

This page was last updated on March 16th 2009.

Any data entered in the guestbook/comments page can be viewed by internet users, unless you set the entry to "Private post for guestbook owner only" at the bottom of the posting page.

Personal information gathered through any e-mail forms on Disneyclips.com is not distributed to any third party. However, if you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., [send a joke](http://www.disneyclips.com/funstuff/sendjoke.html)), your name or screen name may be published. 

* * *

This website uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit it. These companies may use information ( **not** including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

For more information, [**click here**](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  
If you would like to see ads that are more related to your interests, or if you would prefer not to have this information used by these companies, [**click here**](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/view?sig=ACi0TCixsxNxg_oOimkTW93puPi9F5yqGZVJ2eEG_3BOymv0smNT_I0zFNXYGNhiipX-9FSSrAy-0ORSBZ0XiqCHx3O78s3A1M5iU1qs2kYJyb88UgVv0F_YJN_PqcXEG0Uyk4qmi62yvYUmZzjTcXmK3r14O_xyNw&hl=en).

* * *

Information about your IP address, as well as the type of browser and operating system you are using is collected. This is non-personally identifiable information which is used solely to track trends and better understand how visitors use this website. 

Disneyclips.com is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of websites visited through links from this website.

Please be advised that this privacy policy may be changed in the future. Return to this page to see any changes made. 

|  | 

Magical Movies

| |  **Tangled**  
---  
[](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/B004G600A4/disneysworldofwo)| |  [  
Get ready to cheer for "Tangled"!](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/B004G600A4/disneysworldofwo)  
---|---|---  

Updates

April 1st 2011  
35 new cliparts, featuring Cinderella, The Little Mermaid, Beauty and the Beast, Easter, Tangled, The Princess and the Frog, Ariel's Beginning, Weddings, Sleeping Beauty and Snow White.  
  
|
